<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>coc on Open Science Labs</title><link>https://opensciencelabs.org/opensciencelabs2.github.io/tags/coc/</link><description>Recent content in coc on Open Science Labs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://opensciencelabs.org/opensciencelabs2.github.io/tags/coc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contributor Covenant Code of Conduct</title><link>https://opensciencelabs.org/opensciencelabs2.github.io/guidelines/coc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://opensciencelabs.org/opensciencelabs2.github.io/guidelines/coc/</guid><description>
Our Pledge We as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.
We pledge to act and interact in ways that contribute to an open, welcoming, diverse, inclusive, and healthy community.</description></item><item><title>Código de conducta de las mentorías</title><link>https://opensciencelabs.org/opensciencelabs2.github.io/guidelines/coc-mentoring/coc-mentoring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://opensciencelabs.org/opensciencelabs2.github.io/guidelines/coc-mentoring/coc-mentoring/</guid><description>
Código de conducta de las mentorías Al acceder o utilizar los servicios de tutoría de OSL, y por lo tanto formar parte de esta comunidad, usted está de acuerdo en cumplir con nuestro Código de Conducta.
Los participantes se comprometen a no participar en ninguna actividad torticera o criminal y si usted se involucra en dicha actividad, usted entiende que es totalmente responsable en la medida de la ley y que va a contratar a su propio abogado a su propio costo, pagar y todas las multas necesarias y otros costos y se compromete a mantener OSL inofensivo.</description></item></channel></rss>